/*
 * @license
 * Copyright (c) 2014 The Polymer Project Authors. All rights reserved.
 * This code may only be used under the BSD style license found at http://polymer.github.io/LICENSE.txt
 * The complete set of authors may be found at http://polymer.github.io/AUTHORS.txt
 * The complete set of contributors may be found at http://polymer.github.io/CONTRIBUTORS.txt
 * Code distributed by Google as part of the polymer project is also
 * subject to an additional IP rights grant found at http://polymer.github.io/PATENTS.txt
 */

(function() {
  
  window.categories = [
    {
      name: 'Food & Drink',
      id: 'food',
      theme: 'green',
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: [0,1,2]
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: [2]
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: [0,1,2]
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: [2]
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: [0,1,2]
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: [2]
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: [0,1,2]
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: [2]
        },
        {
          type: 'fill-blank', 
          question: 'Can you name the Google product from a 2006 April Fools day prank?',
          start: 'Love is just another search problem. Solve it with Google',
          end: '',
          answer: 'Romance'
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'Which of the following April Fools jokes has Google actually done?',
          options: [
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs',
            'Search for buried treasure in Maps',
            'Google was renamed Topeka',
            'Translate site text to emoji in chrome',
            'Replace youtube videos with animated gifs'
          ],
          answer: [0,1,2]
        },
        {
          type: 'single-select',
          question: 'Which real Google product launched on April Fools Day in 2004?',
          options: [
            'Drive',
            'Calendar',
            'Gmail',
            'Chrome'
          ],
          answer: [2]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: 'General Knowledge',
      id: 'knowledge',
      theme: 'yellow',
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: 'single-select', 
          question: 'When was the first Google I/O?',
          options: [
            '2006',
            '2007',
            '2008',
            '2014'
          ],
          answer: [2]
        },
        {
          type: 'multi-select',
          question: 'What are the 3 I/O themes this year?',
          options: [
            'Doodle',
            'Design',
            'Debug',
            'Develop',
            'Distribute',
            'Decode'
          ],
          answer: [1,3,4]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "History",
      id: 'history',
      theme: "blue",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "Geography",
      id: "geography",
      theme: "red",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "Science & Nature",
      id: "science",
      theme: "green",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "TV & Movies",
      id: "tvmovies",
      theme: "purple",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "Music",
      id: "music",
      theme: "blue",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "Entertainment",
      id: "entertainment",
      theme: "red",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      name: "Sports",
      id: "sports",
      theme: "purple",
      quizzes: [
        {
          type: "single-select",
          question: "Chromebook is made for?",
          options: [
            "Grandma",
            "Kids",
            "Classroom",
            "Everyone"
          ],
          answer: [3]
        }
      ]
    }
  ];
  
})();